

ABOUT ME

I'm Fidalgo, a 25 years old self-taught Javascript Developer, currently living in Leicester.

In October 2018 I decided it was time for a change, so I started to study Javascript before going into work. I quickly started to love Javascript and in January 2019 I decided to take the risk and quit my job. I then studied Javascript until July 2019, where I landed my first job at Mindera UK. I quickly improved my Javascript skills here and transitioned to a Full Stack position.

I always want to learn moreand do more. I'm also a firm believer that we should never settle. I'm hard working, super curious, passionate, committed and a fast learner!

EDUCATION

Communication and Multimedia

Universidade de Trás-os-Montes e Alto Douro - Vila Real, Portugal 09/2014 - 06/2017

EQF Level 4

- Web development (HTML, CSS and PHP);
- Web Design;
- Communication Skills;
- History of Art.

Technical Course of Multimedia

Escola EB 2/3 c/ Secundário PAMF - Murtosa, Portugal 09/2010 - 06/2013

EQF - Level 3

- Video Editing;
- Design
- 3D

SKILLS

html css javascript react js graphql node aws

EXPERIENCE

Javascript Developer

Mindera - Leicester, United Kingdom 07/2019 - Current

- High scalable full-stack e-commerce platform for a big UK Retailer;
- Frontend Application for a Finance company;

Web Developer

Invisual Branding Solutions - Aveiro, Portugal

- -Wordpress projects;
- -Small management apps with PHP;
- -Static websites using HTML5 and CSS3;
- -Mobile Apps using PhoneGap;

Web Department Leader

Núcleo Estudantes Comunicação e Multimédia - Vila Real, Portugal

- -Development of Students Association Website;
- -Wordpress projects;

Freelancer

Olhoshot - Ovar, Portugal

-Developed several websites using HTML, CSS and Wordpress on the freelancing regime;

Internship

Olhoshot - Ovar, Portugal 05/2012 - 06/2012

-Developed several websites using HTML, CSS and Wordpress;

SOCIALS

www.fidalgo.dev hello@fidalgo.dev youtube.com/c/fidalgodev instagram.com/fidalgo.dev linkedin.com/in/fidalgodev twitter.com/fidalgodev